Master.
You did well.
You were behind what happened earlier.
What does it have to do with you?
Who are you?
Just an ordinary medicine seller.
What kind of medicine?
Amulets,
wealth pouches,
lotus bags,
peace charms.
Items that pray for all to be safe,
medicine that cures worldly disasters,
I have it all.
Items that pray for all to be safe?
I wonder if these things
can keep you safe today.
My goods
are naturally useful.
So confident.
Honest with everyone.
Good.
Then let's see how these things of yours
keep you safe today.
Marshes sink all phenomena,
roots lock the light.
Suppress.
You have some skills.
Come again.
It seems
you just have some brute strength.
Monster!
The boss is a monster!
A bunch of trash.
Run!
What?
Scared silly?
If you were human,
I wouldn't know how to deal with you.
But if you reveal your demon form...
So what?
Golden edge shining,
piercing the heavens!
Embrace the origin!
Heaven and earth, shake!
Immortal!
You are
the Liujin Immortal of Three Mountains.
I found you.
It's raining.
That's great.
My brother is awesome.
It's raining.
Look, isn't your brother awesome?
Awesome.
Let's go.
Silver.
Lots of silver.
So much silver.
We're rich!
Chief,
this ill-gotten wealth
should be handed over to the authorities.
That's such a pity.
It still hasn't rained.
Are our offerings not enough?
Chief,
I will go up the mountain tomorrow
to pick some mountain ginseng.
Village chief,
this is far enough.
Wait for me at home.
Stay safe.
Come back soon.
Brother,
come back early.
I'll be waiting for you.
I will return as soon as possible.
Okay.
Stay safe.
Stay safe. Stay safe.
While you were up the mountain,
the bandits came for revenge
and killed your brother.
This wine is really good.
Come.
How much can you drink?
Come on.
You really can't hold your liquor.
What is he doing here?
Why did you kill my brother?
Hero,
we haven't gone down the mountain recently.
Lei Long.
He will definitely die on the mountain.
All these things are ours now.
Mine.
Lei Long.
Let me explain.
It's not what you think.
Human hearts and the demonic path,
what's the difference?
It is this world
that has wronged me.
Die, all of you!
Jie Qianghai.